Izzy: Tell me about your home town.
Ben: Well… it’s a small town in California.
My parents have a farm there.
Izzy: Is it nice?
Ben: It’s very quiet, but I like it.
Izzy: What’s the weather like?
Ben: It’s nice in the summer, but it’s really cold in the winter.
Izzy: Does it snow?
Ben: Yeah, it does. We get a lot of snow.
Izzy: I love snow.
Ben: Me too.
But my favourite time of the year is the fall.
You say ‘autumn’, right? The fall is really beautiful.
Izzy: Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Ben: I have a sister. A twin sister, actually.
Izzy: A twin sister… that’s cool. What’s her name?
Ben: Emma. She’s great.
Izzy: What does she do?
Ben: She works on my parents’ farm.
What about you? Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Izzy: No. I don’t have any brothers or sisters. It’s only me.
Ben: Oh. It’s Jenny. She’s my aunt. She’s calling from the US.
Izzy: Really? Answer it!
Jenny: Hi, Ben.
Ben: Hey, Jenny.
Jenny: How’s London?
Ben: Oh, it’s great.
Jenny: What are you doing now?
Ben: I’m sightseeing… and shopping.
Jenny: Fantastic. Where are you?
Ben: I’m… not sure exactly. I’m with a friend.
Izzy: Hi, Jenny! We’re in Hackney. I’m Izzy. I’m Ben’s friend.
Jenny: Oh, hi!
Izzy: Don’t worry. Ben is fine. He’s with me. I’m showing him the city.
Jenny: I’m happy to hear it! Have a great time, Ben.
Ben: OK, thanks. Say ‘hi’ to Rob and the kids.
Jenny: Bye!
Ben: Bye.
Izzy: She’s nice. Is she your mother’s sister?
Ben: Yeah, she is. She knows London really well. Her husband, Rob, is from here.
Izzy: Oh, really?
Ben: Yeah. Rob’s great.
He’s the love of her life.
Listen, Izzy.
My photography class has a little show next week.
Do you want to come?
Izzy: Um… I don’t know.
Ben: Oh, it’s OK. No problem.
Izzy: No… I’d love to come. Thanks.